<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wikis on CCExtractor</title><link>https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/</link><description>Recent content in Wikis on CCExtractor</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/dokuwiki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/dokuwiki/</guid><description>DokuWiki DokuWiki is a simple to use and highly versatile Open Source wp&amp;gt;wiki software that doesn't require a database. It is loved by users for its clean and readable wiki:syntax. The ease of maintenance, backup and integration makes it an administrator's favorite. Built in access controls and authentication connectors make DokuWiki especially useful in the enterprise context and the large number of doku&amp;gt;plugins contributed by its vibrant community allow for a broad range of use cases beyond a traditional wiki.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/syntax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/syntax/</guid><description>Formatting Syntax doku&amp;gt;DokuWiki supports some simple markup language, which tries to make the datafiles to be as readable as possible. This page contains all possible syntax you may use when editing the pages. Simply have a look at the source of this page by pressing &amp;quot;Edit this page&amp;quot;. If you want to try something, just use the playground page. The simpler markup is easily accessible via quickbuttons, too.
Basic Text Formatting DokuWiki supports bold, //italic//, __underlined__ and monospaced texts.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/welcome/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ccextractor.netlify.app/wiki/welcome/</guid><description>Welcome to your new DokuWiki Congratulations, your wiki is now up and running. Here are a few more tips to get you started.
Enjoy your work with DokuWiki, -- the developers
Create your first pages Your wiki needs to have a start page. As long as it doesn't exist, this link will be red: :start.
Go on, follow that link and create the page. If you need help with using the syntax you can always refer to the syntax page.</description></item></channel></rss>